http://www.ngtechlaw.com/privacy-policy/

General Questions
Client Guide (What to Expect)
Privacy Policy
We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you specifically provide it to us. Except as required by law or expressly authorized by you, we will not provide any personally identifiable information regarding you to any third parties. Any personally identifiable information that you submit to us will be used solely for the purpose of responding to inquiries or requests made by you.
By using this website, you consent to our use of your information as described in this Privacy Statement. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Statement at any time without advance notice. Should any new policy go into effect, we will post it on this site, and the revised Statement will apply only to information collected thereafter.
Privacy Policy
|
Legal Disclaimer
Home |
Attorneys |
Practice |
Press Room |
IP News & Events |
Blog |
Resources |
FAQs |
Contact Us
© Copyright 2011-2020, The Noblitt Group. All Rights Reserved
This site is regulated by the Arizona Rules of Professional Conduct. Do not email information to the firm unless the sender is an existing client because the communication will not create an attorney/client relationship and may not be kept confidential or privileged. Viewing the legal information on this website does not constitute legal advice and does not create an attorney/client relationship. Visitors to this website should consult with an attorney for legal advice. The lawyers of The Noblitt Group, PLLC practice law only in the jurisdictions where they are admitted.
